[Music]
hello welcome to my vlog so for today
we're going to have a product review on
sun life's health insurance plan which
is satellite assurance
sunlight
so sunlight for sure it is a
non-participating so from the word none
participate the ebikes
value savings components is sunlight for
sure
it's a five-year renewable term
insurance plan so ebik's a bihan is
payable for five years
and then coverage for five years and
then it automatically renews
every after five years that provides a
lump sum
amount either upon death or upon
diagnosis
while leaving of a covered critical
illness whichever occurs first
civic sabihin covered ka for a critical
illness benefit quesan left ashore
and then kohindi critical illness you
are also covered
for a life insurance kai sun life for
sure
so whichever comes first dusa de la
banyan coverage is up to age
70 so ebik sabihin you can renew sun
life assure up to age
70 only
okay issue age society
for sun life ashore uh
is from 18 to 60 years old for both
non-smokers and smokers so indeep
and over 60 years old face amount of sun
life assure minimum per life
is 500k and then the maximum is 15
million
the death and the critical illness
benefit is hundred percent of the face
amount so since
uh sun life ashore can be a coverage for
critical illness or can be also coverage
for death
whichever comes first so 100 of the face
amount
benefit what are the available riders or
applicable riders for sun life assured
its accidental death benefit and then
the total disability benefit which
this is the weaver of premium so let's
see
covered critical illness so here are the
36 critical illness not covered
for sun life ashore
so let's have a sample illustration or
sample proposal for sunlight for sure
so for example a whole female non-smoker
applying for sun life ashore my face
amount is five hundred thousand then i
have a rider accidental death benefit
which is
five hundred thousand then and then
total disability benefit which is my
waiver of premium so your accidental
death benefit
it will just add up the surface amount
now 500
000 if the reason of death is by
accident
okay someone giving one million you're
gigging that benefit go
first unless are sure okay so from here
from the illustration i applied at 25
years old and then i am covered
till age 30 for sun life i sure so
that's five years
pain period and protection period so
ebik sabine i will pay for five years
for the sun life ashore and then covered
in a hole
for five years skysand left ashore so
five years now whichever occurs first if
ever my own
diagnosis of a critical illness i will
get the 500 000
rate go or on premium go for my first
five years
with sun life assure so for your first
for sun life usher an annual premium co
every year is four thousand nine hundred
ninety
eight in premium call for the first five
years every year i enjoyed being a buy
it go
it's a plan and then if i want to renew
or since the plan
is automatically renewable after five
years at the name
on my second uh five years sahanas oh
yeah six to ten year is
five thousand seventy nine so nag mahal
nasha since the business
age go up and renewable so when i renew
since 25 to 30 language first five years
at the age of 31
every year till year 10 or till age
35 and then so on and so forth ayana
shahangan safan kailan kosha
so for face amount of 500 000 with
accidental death benefit and total
disability benefit at all manner rates
or premium for male non-smoker which is
annual
and then for female non-smoker and well
then
so based on age ayansha 25 years old
5024 male
and then for female 4 thousand nine
hundred ninety and then
so on and so forth
every time namaste
amount would be higher than 500 000. so
if
one million peanut mouse advisor will of
course expect
us based on this
is almost 5 000.
500 a month
so what are the pros and the cons of sun
life assurance
so of course affordable premium so
samurai
hovered for 36 critical illness with
life insurance pressure so high
technical
diagnosis of a covered critical illness
melancholic life insurance that's
an accidental death benefit and then
total disability benefit
and then perfection for those people
temporarily need london health insurance
because a temporary coverage
perfect and then maximum coverage
so again no savings component just like
sun safer life
it's purely protection so either uh
covered critical illness upon diagnosis
of that
or that benefit lanta lagasha
and then madame maglab since
hash value so happy
[Music]
so what are the frequently asked
questions about sunlight ashore so
covered bajo for illness so the answer
is no
once the critical illness has been
claimed the policy terminates
any of one of the 36 critical illness
only so islam
is illness
amount is 500 000 hindi forward now
500 000 each for that illness okay so
any of the 36 critical illness
the policy will terminate
[Music]
whichever comes first
face amount is also the death benefit of
your plan zodibasabe
whichever comes first if diagnosis of a
critical illness or upon death
of the insured so parent dual purpose
narinja
so again the plan is purely insurance no
cash value or return of
investment because it's a
non-participating term insurance plan
so you're just only paying for peace of
mind
if something happens or the
for critical illness at least prepared
by numerous
health insurance plans
savings component
anong accredited
so regardless of the hospital you will
receive the lump sum
amount as long as the diagnosis is a
covered critical illness so
regardless diagnosis
critical illness you will receive your
benefit you will receive the critical
illness benefit
regardless since this is a health
insurance plan
and not hmo so yeah
thank you for watching so that's all for
today for some life assurance so if you
have a few more questions
you can message me at my personal fb or
staffing facebook page
in the description box and if you
haven't subscribed on my youtube channel
please do subscribe and don't forget to
click the bell button beside it so
you'll be notified every time i upload a
new video you can also watch my video a
vlog
and term insurance blog the link is on
the description box there
so long thank you and see you on my next
one